"Death of Antonio" also known as "The Sequel to Black God, White Devil"
The mysterious outlaw, Cangacero, disappeared from northeastern Brazil in 1940.
The greatest Cangacero of all time, Lampiao, led them.
He waged a 25-year-long anti-government struggle, and even today, there are still new Cangaceros emerging, trying to relive the glory of Lampiao.
Batch after batch of Cangaceros continue to emerge, attempting to recreate the former glory of Lampiao.
St. George is the most popular Catholic saint in Brazil.
In both Brazilian and African religions, a warrior named Oxossi is equally revered.
Therefore, both St. George and Oxossi are referred to as São Geraldo.
Meaning the holy warrior or the holy fighter.
This film is inspired by the mythical battle of: